key_of_c = [{'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'E1', 'answer': 'F', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'B1', 'answer': 'C', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'e1', 'answer': 'F', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'A2', 'answer': 'B', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'D2', 'answer': 'E', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'G2', 'answer': 'A', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'E3', 'answer': 'G', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'A3', 'answer': 'C', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'D3', 'answer': 'F', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'B3', 'answer': 'D', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'e3', 'answer': 'G', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'G4', 'answer': 'B', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'E5', 'answer': 'A', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'A5', 'answer': 'D', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'D5', 'answer': 'G', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'G5', 'answer': 'C', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'B5', 'answer': 'E', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'e5', 'answer': 'A', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'B6', 'answer': 'F', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'E7', 'answer': 'B', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'A7', 'answer': 'E', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'D7', 'answer': 'A', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'G7', 'answer': 'D', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'e7', 'answer': 'B', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'E8', 'answer': 'C', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'A8', 'answer': 'F', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'B8', 'answer': 'G', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'e8', 'answer': 'C', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'D9', 'answer': 'B', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'G9', 'answer': 'E', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'E10', 'answer': 'D', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'A10', 'answer': 'G', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'D10', 'answer': 'C', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'G10', 'answer': 'F', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'B10', 'answer': 'A', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'e10', 'answer': 'D', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'E12', 'answer': 'E', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'A12', 'answer': 'A', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'D12', 'answer': 'D', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'G12', 'answer': 'G', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'B12', 'answer': 'B', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'e12', 'answer': 'E', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'E13', 'answer': 'F', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'B13', 'answer': 'C', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'e13', 'answer': 'F', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'A14', 'answer': 'B', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'D14', 'answer': 'E', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'G14', 'answer': 'A', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'E15', 'answer': 'G', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'A15', 'answer': 'C', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'D15', 'answer': 'F', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'B15', 'answer': 'D', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}, {'deck_name': 'key_of_c', 'question': 'e15', 'answer': 'G', 'level': 'red', 'seen_on': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8), 'show_again_after': datetime.date(2024, 11, 8)}]